(Sheldon:)There should be no value
to his pseudo-celebrity here!
(Sheldon:)And even at
Star Trek conventions,
(Sheldon:)they only let him in
if he helps set up!
(Leonard:)Calm down, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)I will not calm down.
(Sheldon:)This affront to justice and
decency cannot go unanswered.
(Sheldon:)As Captain Jean-Luc Picard
once said,
"The line must be drawn here!
"This far, no farther!"
(Leonard:)Had to wake him up
from his nap, didn't you?
(Bernadette:)You know what I really love
about Howard?
(Bernadette:)His chest hair.
(Penny:)Howard has a
hairy chest?
(Bernadette:)No, just the one.
(Bernadette:)But it's really long.
(Penny:)Okay, there you go--
Sultry Sunrise Red.
(Penny:)What do you think?
(Amy:)My nails have never
looked so pretty before.
(Amy:)Get it off.
(Raj:)Oh, oh, uh, looks like
they're getting ready